(Penny:)Is that true?
(Leonard:)-It was the only way to make him happy.
-Why'd you have to make him happy?
(Leonard:)Because when he wasn't happy
we wanted to kill him.
That was even a plan.
(Leonard:)We were going to throw
his Kindle outside.
(Leonard:)And when he went to get it, lock
the door and let him freeze to death.
(Sheldon:)-That seems like a bit of an overreaction.
-No.
The overreaction was to tie your limbs
to four different sled-dog teams...
...and yell, "Mush!"
(Leonard:)Look, we kept the original data.
You can still publish the actual results.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but the actual results
are unsuccessful.
I sent an e-mail
to everyone at the university...
...explaining I confirmed
string theory...
(Sheldon:)...and forever changed
man's understanding of the universe.
Oh. See, yeah, you probably
shouldn't have done that.
(Leonard:)So write another e-mail.
Set the record straight. It's no big deal.
(Sheldon:)You're right, Leonard.
That's not a big deal.
(Sheldon:)All you did was lie to me,
destroy my dream...